shesheme.com 2019-06-24

# SheSheMe.com

Shesheme.com is firmly committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information. This Privacy Policy outlines our efforts to maintain your privacy. 

**Why Did You Receive An Email From Us?**

You receive mailings from shesheme.com for two possible reasons:

  * Your email address has been provided to us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"); 
  * You have registered or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. 

We respect your time and attention by controlling the content and frequency of our mailings. You will receive an average of one to four emails PER MONTH from shesheme.com. 

**What information we collect:**

  * First and last name (optional) 
  * Email address (required) 
  * Phone Number (optional) 

**How Your Privacy Is Protected**

shesheme.com uses security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data you have provided to us. 

Cookie Policy  
  
We and some of our partners may make use of cookies (small text files placed on your computer’s hard disk by our server). They are used to collect traffic information such as the number of visits to our site and pages visited. This  
information will be used to assess how visitors are using our services. This data will also allow us to manage the functionality of the site. You can disable cookies at any time if your browser permits.

**Usage and Sharing**

We do not sell, share, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance written permission or unless ordered by a court of law. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information, for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you. We may transfer the information that you have provided to us if shesheme.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, shesheme.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**How Can You Stop Receiving Email From She She Me?**

Each email sent contains an easy and automated way for you to stop receiving email messages from shesheme.com in the future. If you would like to do this – to “opt-out” — simply follow the links at the bottom of every email message. 

If you have received unwanted or unsolicited email sent via the shesheme.com system or purporting to be sent via the shesheme.com system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to [customerservice@shesheme.com](mailto:customerservice@shesheme.com). We will look into the matter immediately.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact [customerservice@shesheme.com](mailto:customerservice@shesheme.com). 

**  
Privacy Policy Changes**

This policy was last updated on May 22, 2018.
